[{"answer": "That's absolutely rude.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 17}, {"answer": "You know, we'd definitely like a win.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "How important strategically is winning Ohio?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "I mean, does he feel like he takes two steps forward then two back and so on, that it's been a real uphill battle when he wasn't maybe expecting it?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "I think he's not on the PIERS", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Why do they're not getting the real Mitt Romney, do you think?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "I haven't resisted your charms at all.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Why have you resisted me for so long?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "It is, it is.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 154, "question": "Tell me about the reality of being a presidential candidate because it's incredibly hard work, isn't it?", "qSentId": 153}, {"answer": "My opinion is, I think it will be a determining day because there's so many delegates up for grabs.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Will it be a determining day, do you think, or are we going to be here in a month with things still undecided?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "Well, the process is very good.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "And it maybe that if Mitt Romney was to prevails here or Rick Santorum, it helps them to have this long battle?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "I am very happy to get behind any of these candidates because I want to have a unifying voice.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "Are you disappointed that there is no bona fide Tea Party candidate left in the race?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "I like Rick Santorum a lot but I like Mitt Romney, I like Newt Gingrich, I like Ron Paul.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 205, "question": "Would that be a misreading?", "qSentId": 204}, {"answer": "I think -- I think my opinions were fairly forthright throughout the debate and I felt, quite honestly, I was the perfect candidate for America.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "Who do you most agree with?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "I mean if you're so vehemently in the vanguard against Obama care, presumably Mitt Romney is the least of the four candidates that you would personally endorse, right?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "Well, what I thought at first is that this is a 3D example of what Obama care is going to mean in every America's life from now on because essentially for the first time in the history of the country we have one person who will be a health care czar, who will not only dictate what we get in health care but more importantly what we won't get in health care.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Michele Bachmann, were you as appalled as I was by Rush Limbaugh's rhetoric?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "No, what I'm saying is that --", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "I think that it's -- it's unnatural.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Do you think homosexuality is a sin?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not -- I'm here as a member of Congress.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "What do you think of his comments?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "I am not here as anybody's judge.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "But do you agree with him?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Well, there is still -- every state in the country that has put this up to the vote, people have voted for marriage between a man and a woman.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "This is one of the fastest sea changes in public opinion that people can remember in America, isn't it?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "I believe that everyone under the law here in the United States has the right to the same level of protections under our Constitution.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "Just equality of respect?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Honestly, I think I have had enough of the conversation.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Would you agree with those comments, personally?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "For you.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "It is a lively horse, though, isn't it?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Everyone wants the best.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "Is it snobbery to want your kids to go to college?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Listen, Piers, I have been a mother of 28 children from every level of capability.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Was he wrong to use that word?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "I'm not on the left or right.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 587, "question": "They're -- oh, really, Piers?", "qSentId": 586}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Aren't you glad you did?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "So respect on both sides is what we need to get to?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "Lewis, I just had Michele Bachmann on, who called me rude and was indignant because I had the impertinence to suggest that she was judgmental, when some would argue she's the most judgmental woman in American politics.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "What planet are we on?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "I thought it was quite interesting, the reaction to the Kirk Cameron comments on my show, because I must say, I didn't expect it to erupt the way that it did.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 654, "question": "Did they burn their hands on Bunsen Burners?", "qSentId": 653}, {"answer": "It's that whole thing of, you know -- it's -- you know, being Jewish, you know, you kind of -- I know enough about Christianity to know you're not being a Christian.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 662, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 661}, {"answer": "It's already done.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Why are you worried about?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 681, "question": "What did you make up of the rush Limbaugh furor?", "qSentId": 680}, {"answer": "I think it's one of the most spectacular races I've ever watched, if it was like maybe 1958.", "docId": "120305pmt", "aSentId": 686, "question": "What are your overall thoughts about this Republican race?", "qSentId": 685}]